http://www.thetech.org/policies

Skip to main content
Menu
Plan Your Visit
Plan Your VisitExhibits
ExhibitsBioDesign StudioBody MotionBody Worlds DecodedCyber DetectivesExploration Gallery(Temporarily Closed)Innovations in Health CareReboot RealitySocial RobotsThe Tech for Global GoodThe Tech StudioExperiences
ExperiencesBirdlySensory Friendly HoursStanford at The TechGirl ScoutsParkingCalendarBirthday PartiesIMAX
IMAXNow ShowingIMAX for EducatorsAbout IMAXIMAX at homeMembers
MembersMembership OptionsEvents and PerksBuy or Renew a MembershipView Your AccountEducation
EducationBowers Institute: Educator Resources
Bowers Institute: Educator ResourcesLesson Plans and ToolsProfessional DevelopmentGirls at The TechVirtual Learning at The TechThe Tech Academies
The Tech AcademiesTech Academies FellowshipSTEM PathwaysOur impactSummer InstituteThe Tech ChallengeEducator MembershipsFamily Math & EngineeringSummer Camps at The Tech InteractiveSupport Us
Support UsOur ProgramsWays to GiveOur SupportersVolunteerBecome a MemberLegacy GivingPrivate and Corporate Event Rentals
Private and Corporate Event RentalsFull Facility RentalUpper LevelLower LevelNew Venture Hall/LobbyIMAX Dome TheaterRooftop TerraceThe Bowers InstituteSubmit Rental InquiryAbout Us
About UsAbout The Tech InteractiveMedia RoomSocial MediaLeadership TeamFinancial ReportsJobsContactThe Tech CafeThe Tech ChallengeThe Tech for Global GoodDonate Now
Search
Search
Policies
You are hereHome / PoliciesPolicies
Ticket Donation PolicySuspended until further notice.
Refund/Exchange Policy on TicketsALL SALES ARE FINAL. NOT TRANSFERABLE. NO REFUNDS. Restrictions: Ticket is a revocable license. Any violation of law, or any inappropriate behavior by the user of this ticket may result in revocation of the license with no refund of the purchase price or any associated charges. No refunds, exchanges, or time extensions on expired tickets. Ticket is not redeemable for cash, not for resale, and not valid with any other offer. The Tech Interactive is not responsible for any lost, duplicate, or stolen ticket(s). All prices listed are in U.S. dollars.TICKET IS FOR PURCHASE OR TRANSFER BY ELECTRONIC MEANS ONLY. PURCHASE OF TICKET FROM OR SALES BY A THIRD PARTY IS NOT AUTHORIZED. TICKETS NOT PURCHASED ELECTRONICALLY CARRY A HIGH RISK OF BEING FRAUDULENT. THE TECH INTERACTIVE RESERVES THE RIGHT TO REQUIRE PHOTO I.D. FOR ENTRY. EACH BARCODE IS ELECTRONICALLY GENERATED UNIQUE AND IS VALID FOR ONE SCAN DURING LISTED DATES / TIMES ONLY. TICKET IS VOID IF ALTERED IN ANY WAY. THE TECH INTERACTIVE RESERVES THE RIGHT TO REFUSE SERVICE TO FRAUDULENT OR SUSPECT TICKET HOLDERS.
Disclaimer and Statement of LiabilityUse of The Tech Interactive web siteThe Tech, a not-for-profit science and technology center, operates a web site on the World Wide Web under the name The Tech Interactive Web Site. Authorization to view, copy, print and distribute the content of The Tech web site is subject to approval of The Tech, and must meet the following conditions: (i) it is used for educational, non-commercial purposes only; (ii) any copy or portion must include The Tech copyright notice at the bottom of this page; (iii) no modifications are made; and (iv) The Tech reserves the right to revoke such authorization at any time, and any such use shall be discontinued upon written notice from The Tech.
Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) governs information that visitors to The Tech Interactive’s website, www.thetech.org (the “Site”), provide to us or that we learn from your use of the Site. The Privacy Policy tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances share your information. Information the The Tech Interactive Collects from Website VisitorsRegistration information. When you register for an account on our Site, we ask you to provide contact information, including your name and email address. You may optionally provide demographic information (such as age and gender), and unique identifiers (such as membership or promotional identification numbers), which enables us to provide a more personalized experience on our Site.Purchase information. If you purchase tickets through our online order forms, we collect and store contact information, including name and shipping address, and financial information, including credit card number and expiration date.Information collected when you visit our Site. We automatically collect certain information when you use our Site, including information about how you use the Site and your IP address.When you visit the Site, we collect certain information through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that Web servers place on an internet user’s computer that are designed to store basic information and to recognize your browser. For example, we set a cookie when you use our Site so that you don’t have to log in with a password when you visit our Site again. We also use Google Analytics cookies for data analytics purposes, and you can find more information on how Google uses data from these cookies at google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. Please consult your web browser to learn the proper way to modify its cookie settings. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Site, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Site to their fullest potential.How The Tech Uses Information We Collect from Website VisitorsTo provide and operate the Site.To monitor and analyze usage and trends.To personalize, improve, and promote the Site, such as providing content or features that match your demographics or interests.To communicate with you, including to send you communications about services on our Site in which you have expressed interest, service announcements, administrative messages, promotional messages, and our email newsletters. From time to time, you may be subscribed to new categories of email newsletters. You can adjust your contact information by visiting theMy Account section of our website or opt out of receiving promotional communications by visitingMy Account or following the unsubscribe instructions contained in emails you receive from us.To process your payment. Your payment information is used for billing purposes and to fill your ticket orders. We work with a third party service provider to process your payment. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use your contact information to get in touch with you.How The Tech Shares Information We Collect from Website VisitorsService providers. The Tech may disclose the information we collect, including personally identifiable information, to our service providers to perform functions and process user data on our behalf, including to manage transactions, payments, and purchases, and to otherwise support the Site.Aggregated information. We may share aggregated information that does not identify you with third parties for various data purposes, including understanding site usage patterns and improving site functionality.Advertising partners. We may also work with third party advertising partners to show you advertisements we think may be of interest to you. These third party partners collect non-personally identifying information from you through cookies when you visit our website and other websites. If you do not wish to receive our personalized ads, please visit the opt-out pages of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance[2]  to learn about how you may opt out of receiving personalized ads from member companies.Third Party LinksThe Site may contain links to other websites, products, or services that The Tech does not own or operate.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these third parties before providing any information to them.  The Tech is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties.  If you choose to visit or use any third-party products, websites, or services, including those offered by our third party service providers or other partners, please be aware that this Privacy Policy will not apply to your activities or any information you disclose to these third parties.Children’s PrivacyThe Tech does not knowingly collect personally information from children under the age of 13.  If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete this information. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us at please contact us at info@thetech.org.Special Note to International Website VisitorsThe Site is hosted in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Site from the European Union or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States for storage and processing. By providing your information you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Changes and Updates to This Privacy PolicyWe may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the effective date above. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on our Site or by sending you an email or other notification. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the information we collect.  Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.
Warranties and DisclaimersThe Tech intends the information contained in The Tech web site to be accurate and reliable. However, errors may occasionally occur. Therefore, all information and materials are provided "AS IS." In no event will The Tech be liable for any indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages arising out of the use of the information contained in The Tech web site.
Feedback and ResponsesAny comments or materials sent to The Tech web site including feedback data, such as questions, comments, suggestions and any other response, shall be deemed to be non-confidential. The Tech shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such response, The Tech shall be free to use, reproduce, distribute and publicly display such response without limitation. The Tech Interactive shall also be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such response for any purpose whatsoever.
Third Party Companies and ProductsMention of third-party companies and products on The Tech Interactive web site is for informational purposes only and constitutes neither an endorsement nor a recommendation.
